Pink Slip! Pink Slip!
Text from Mom:
"Hi, honey. I noticed
you haven't chimed in
on the family chat."
Text from Mom:
"Maybe we can all FaceTime?"
"I'm just about to
record a new episode."
Hi. Welcome back.
I'm Dr. Tess Coleman,
and this is
Rebelling with Respect.
Today on the podcast,
we are talking
about a relationship dynamic
that is very close
to my heart.
"Grand co-parenting."
When my daughter, Anna,
chose to become a single mom,
it changed our family forever.
Ryan! Cloffice. Recording.
Sorry!
As a grandma, I was
able to step up and help her.
Harper!
Harper, this is
your 30-minute warning
that we're leaving for school.
Harp?
This is now
your 20-minute warning.
Ten minutes.
Yes, confirm
the recording sessions.
But know that I know she can
sell out more than the Greek.
And yes, I know
how many seats there are.
Harper! I really wanna
respect your space,
but I'm curious as to why
you're not out here yet.
You have five minutes!
Being someone that
your loved one can lean on
is the most important
relationship there is.
Ryan,
I'm getting so good at this!
No.
No, no, no!
Oh, it didn't record!
Moth--
Hi, Mom.
Now is not a great time.
I'm just...
I know, but I finished
my podcast early,
so I'm offering
to do drop-off.
No. It's okay. I've got
everything under control.
Harper, you had to be up
ten minutes ago!
Prepare to be triggered!
Harper!
Let's catch one more.
Dude,
these waves are unreal.
I love our lives!
Yo, are we skipping
first period?
Oh, shoot. We gotta go.
- Harper!
- What?
I'm literally ready.
Barely. Barely.
I made your favorite lunch.
How was pickleball yesterday?
Did you beat 'em?
We say "annihilated."
Mom, I told you
I could take her.
I know, sweetheart.
But I saw on your stories
that you were working
at the studio late,
and so I decided to take her.
You know, it would be healthy
for you to unfollow me.
And I work late all the time.
I can still take her.
Anna, let's pause and reframe.
When you decided
to be a single mom,
I told you I would support you
a hundred percent.
Well, this is me supporting
you a hundred percent.
Okay, you know what?
I'm coming too.
We can both do drop-off
this morning.
- Mom.
- No, go on. You can go.
- Just let them...
- Oh, okay, you're not going.
- Mom.
- You're gonna go.
You're not...
Nobody's gonna go.
I'm gonna go!
- So what's up, kiddo?
- Nothing.
- Okay, spill it.
- All right.
My new lab partner
is the absolute worst.
She's the new girl,
here for the year.
I mean, ugh,
she thinks
she's so much better
than everyone
because she's British,
which she has to remind you of
every five seconds.
Like no one's ever been
from England before.
So my dad opened
his third restaurant in Paris,
and that's how I met
my French boyfriend,
Philippe Henri.
- Philippe Henri.
- Ooh, la-la.
He's French and a model.
You've seriously been
to Paris Fashion Week?
Anna Wintour scowled at me.
- Seriously?
- What's Paris like?
Oh, it's lovely.
I go all the time.
Ignore the British girl.
After this year, you won't
have to see her anymore.
Nice advice from a therapist.
Well, I'm not her therapist.
I'm her Gram.
All right, well,
this has been real.
Please drive away
like you don't know me.
Make good choices!
You are so lame.
Lame!
Are you
ready for laboratory today?
Shut your mouth.
Fun bonus round today.
Never trust an atom. Why?
'Cause they make up
everything.
Here all day, folks.
You're supposed to
put your goggles on
before we start.
The goggles are giving Minion.
Yeah. We're not,
like, Minions.
So, no, thank you.
But they're perfect for you.
It's like
the Revolutionary War
was for nothing.
Today, remember,
these are dangerous chemicals.
Maybe we should use
not-dangerous chemicals?
How about you do
your actual share of the work
instead of doodling?
It's called designing.
The measurements
have to be precise.
This experiment is so simple.
In the UK,
we did this in primary school.
The only reason
people think you're smart
is because of
your obnoxious accent.
At least people think
I'm clever.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're smart. Figure it out.
- Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Oh!
- That was not precise!
- That's not precise at all!
Oh. Principal Waldman!
I don't know, Mom.
I don't know why
the principal called me,
but I'm here.
So you don't need to come.
You know what?
I can't find what I was gonna
tell you about.
I'll call you...
- Sorry.
- It's totally my fault.
No, no, no. I-I wasn't
looking where I was going.
Oh.
Are you okay?
- Your phone.
- Yeah, I...
Yeah, I don't know
how to turn this thing off.
Yeah, I'm not sure, either.
I think, maybe...
- I think you got it.
- Is it off?
- Yeah. It's just...
- Oh, thank you.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
Um, my daughter
just started here,
and I admit I'm quite lost.
Would you happen to know
where the chemistry lab is?
This is serious. Someone
could have been injured.
I'm sure it was just
an accident.
It seems to me
a misunderstanding.
Harper seems so...
lovely.
Oh. Well, Lily seems so genuine and kind.
Wow. I certainly never had two parents
come in here and be this attractive.
I meant "attentive."
Oh.
Uh, Lily and I are
definitely going to reflect
on how to do better.
This is all Harper and I
are going to think about.
We're very, very committed.
Especially as a single-parent household.
Oh, us too.
- We're single. Parent.
- Great.
I mean, uh...
- I'm a single parent, yeah.
- Single parent. Great.
- Yeah. You know what I mean.
- Yes. Same. Me too.
Single.
Single parent. Guilty.
Great.
I'm single too.
Oh, my God... Should we meet up?
Perhaps our daughters
should get to know each other?
Maybe, like, Wednesdays,
after 6:00. Get a little wine?
Talk about these badass kids?
Harper would really like that.
Over dinner?
Dinner sounds perfect.
I'm on it.
Petit Trois? Yes,
can I have a table for two?
Private. In the back.
Do you guys have any allergies?
- No.
No. No allergies.
Okay, you came here early.
Spill it.
There's just no time.
Bachelorette party, dance rehearsal,
final fitting, rehearsal lunch.
And, oh, my wedding.
You have a lot on your plate.
Big day. Deep breath.
There's so much to do
before Sunday.
Anna, let us know
how we can help.
Maybe someone could help me
memorize my wedding vows.
How about this? I'll help you.
"I, Anna, take you, Eric,
a man that I have been dating
for six months,
but might uproot
my entire life
and move to London,
where we have no family
and an avocado costs $11."
Perhaps you should
add something about
my undying patience
for teenage rebellion.
Spot on about the avocado.
Oh. That wasn't about you.
It was actually about my mom's
other British fiancé.
She's a comedian today.
- Just today, though.
- I see. Yeah.
Right, Harper?
I have been practicing
our first dance.
Wait till you see
what I have cooking.
Ooh, I see what you did there.
I missed you since yesterday.
Ew.
Trevor Travis
just dropped a new single.
I think we can all guess
who it might be about.
Hello?
I had my pastry chef make
sticky toffee pudding pavlova
for the bake sale.
Just what
every teenager loves. Pavlova.
Agreed. Teenagers these days,
sophisticated palates.
Yes, well, this pastry chef
was up at 4:00 a.m.
baking old-fashioned
chocolate chip cookies
from scratch, with no staff.
Four hours for cookies?
I think we need to
get you a staff.
They just needed to cool.
Stand up straight.
Good posture.
Okay. And do you know
how bad this is for you?
Seriously, eat this.
Say, "Thanks, Mom."
I saw that, Harper.
Any day now.
Just trying to keep us
on a schedule here.
Oi. Well,
we wouldn't want
to be off schedule, innit?
Step, and...
Hi, Lil!
It's Lily.
Lily, back seat.
Can't Grams just take me?
No, this will be good bonding
for everyone.
Well, I bond best with Lily
when we're
not around each other,
and I don't have to
look at her face.
Yeah,
I love sitting next to you.
Reminds me that I'm amazing.
Seat belts, girls.
All right. All right.
- I got you.
- You got me.
- Good morning.
- We're ready to go.
Good morning. Car's all set.
Up the coast, Route 1?
- Yeah?
- Yeah? What do you think?
I'm not saying I don't
not want to go on the trip.
I'm just saying
that Anna's wedding
has put me behind
with my patients,
which has been
very disruptive.
- Uh-huh.
- And... And, of course,
they keep adding dates
to my book tour,
which, you know,
it's out of my control.
And I'm just saying
I need a little time.
Look, girls.
We're trying to hear you.
Just try and hear us?
Oh, no.
I hear you trying
to pull me away
from my family and my friends.
I mean, who even gets to surf
before school in London?
You can surf
on the river Thames.
Really?
No, you dipstick.
- Girls.
- It's a city.
- You need to--
- Okay, girls. Girls.
It's our decision.
Eric and I will do
what's right for the family.
- Hmm.
- Family?
Yes, this family.
- Don't say it like that.
- Don't say--
- That sounds really cringe.
- Don't tell me
what to say and how to say.
Harper, relax.
Don't be so dramatic.
Lily.
- Stop gaslighting.
- What?
You don't even know
what that means.
I don't wanna
look at your face anymore.
You know
what that means, right?
- I think I know what it means.
- Yeah. I knew you did.
That explains why
you talk rubbish.
For the bake sale,
every table must have...
Okay.
...a gluten-free option,
an egg-free option...
Please don't slam the...
door.
Well, at least
we don't have to bring them
to our immigration interview
tomorrow.
Don't be stressed.
They'll come round.
Yeah, let them take
all the time they need.
He sounds great.
I'll be back in a bit.
- Here's Ella's schedule.
- Thank you.
Oh, send those
to the tour manager, please.
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay? Because I'm...
- I'm a pop star on the rise.
- Okay.
So I wanna
do the album, you know.
We can come in here
after midnight.
I got the keys to the studio.
- How's it going?
- Oh, good morning.
Actually, it's literally not.
It's a bad morning.
It's a very bad morning.
Not for me,
personally, but for you.
Why, what happened?
Trevor dumped Ella.
And he already released
a song about it.
- Anna!
- Oh.
Yeah, and he dumped her
in a text.
- Yeah, I got this.
- Toxic icon.
I'll get in the booth, and
I'ma just lay it all down...
Okay, so Trevor wrote a song.
But I'm sure
it's not as bad as you think.
It's called
"Better Than the Last One."
It's about me.
Okay, but that title,
it could be about anyone.
It says, parentheses, "Ella."
Let's just focus on the songs
that you're gonna perform
on Saturday.
Performing! Yay!
I can't sing those songs.
I wrote them about Trevor.
I put my heart
and soul into them.
No, a 44-year-old Dutch music
producer wrote those songs.
♪ She's nothing like my ex ♪
This is a hit! This is...
I can't even
stop moving my body.
- Shh!
- Look, my chest
- is just gyrating. I can't...
- Off!
Oh, turn it off.
Turn... All right.
What is that?
Did you learn that from Oprah?
Join the Environmental Club.
Come over.
We have the best cookies.
Welcome to the great
Sunset Ridge Bake-Off.
Shouldn't these be more
prominently featured?
Bon Appétit literally profiled
my dad's restaurant
for these pastries.
I think they're nice
and prominent over here.
Uh, they're gourmet.
They're soggy-bottomed.
You know what? I think I see
the perfect spot for yours.
- Just...
- Dude!
- Those were Gram's!
- Come on.
You know what? I think I know
the perfect place to put this.
You wouldn't dare.
Oh.
Yeah. Perfect.
Nice caramelization.
Oh. Just...
Oh, my God.
Food fight!
Oh, no!
They're
attacking us from above!
We need the high ground!
On my signal!
Too far, Harper.
Stop it!
Put that down! Stop it.
Give me that. Give me that.
Put that down. Stop it!
No, not the strudel!
Please! Or the tart.
Stop it! That got in my mouth!
Hey!
You want a fight?
Let's fight!
Who started...
the food fight?
Congratulations, you two.
You just got everybody in here
in-school suspension.
Thanks a lot.
Is this key lime pie?
Yeah, I baked it fresh
this morning.
Well, you gotta take me
to the emergency room
because I'm very allergic
to key lime pie.
♪ I just keep on coming back ♪
♪ I'm your good
And I'm your... ♪
Is this you?
♪ Baby, our love was made... ♪
Oh, uh...
That's not supposed to
be in there.
- Was it for Pink Slip?
- Hmm.
I saw them at the Troubadour
last year.
Could I sing your song
this weekend?
Oh, no.
You'll have way better stuff
than something I wrote.
I wrote that
after I left Pink Slip anyway.
Okay. I got this.
Yes, you got this.
Opening your world tour
at the Wiltern
is a big show for you. Huge.
For the both of us.
The girls are struggling with
this transition, and just...
just take it from a parent
who has been in your shoes.
I know, Tess, between losing
Lily's mum and moving here...
Yes, and being ripped away
from the home she grew up in.
Oh, I'm sorry. Are we talking
about Lily or about Harper?
Harp? Lily?
That is really annoying.
- No, it's just...
- Hey. What the...
What's going on?
- Darling...
- No one's hurt.
I went to the school...
Please let me
just handle this.
Anna, there's been
an incident at school
between the girls.
It was really bad.
- What bad? How bad? Oh--
- I've got this.
Girls, apologize
to each other now, please.
Ooh, honey, forced apologies
is never a way
to resolve conflict.
- That...
- But...
We need to make space for them
to express how they feel.
Harper, how do you feel?
I feel...
sorry.
And, Lily, how do you feel?
I feel...
...sorry too.
That's great.
- Great.
- See?
Sorry that my future
stepsister is a complete twit.
I'm sorry that my future
stepsister is a shallow idiot.
- Oh, am I? Really?
- New plan!
No more holding space
for feelings.
You two are gonna have
a lovely time
at my bachelorette tonight.
You're gonna get along
because we're a family,
and families love each other!
And for that, Harper,
just for that look,
you two earned yourself
a sleepover at Gram's.
Huh? Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Why am I the punishment?
I'm the fun one.
- I have board games.
- Mom.
I have Parcheesi.
And you're gonna braid
each other's hair
in a non
cultural-appropriating way
and like it.
What is Parcheesi?
- It's a game.
- I'm not quite sure.
You move around the board.
You shake the dice.
You remember the sound
of the dice?
Oh, it's amazing.
You get these dice,
and you shake 'em
in your hand,
- you move around the board.
- Oh, Grams.
It's really fun.
I also have Boggle!
You stay on your side,
and I'll stay on mine.
Gladly.
Harper, look,
I know you think
I don't get it, but I do.
And it's still just gonna
be you and me.
If you go to London,
I'm staying here with Grams.
- She said it was cool.
- She what?
Hey, Anna! Did you remove me
as Harper's secondary contact?
Did you tell Harper that she
could stay here with you
if we decided to
move to London?
- Are you serious right now?
- Whoa. Are you serious?
- Okay, okay.
- Why are you--
What is serious
is that you and Eric need to
keep the girls in Los Angeles.
Lily just needs some guidance.
The only guidance
I need from you
is to show me
to the other bathroom.
I'm very sorry, Lily.
I didn't know--
You don't know anything
about what I need
or how I feel,
or the fashion school
back home that I wanna go to.
Oh!
Yep. Just you and me, Mom.
Great.
Welcome, everyone,
to the bachelorette party
of our girl, Anna.
Mom, for real?
Why would you?
- Haven't changed.
- Not a bit.
- Anna!
- It's so funny.
Get it, girl!
I remember that six-pack.
- Yeah, who is that?
- So handsome.
That is Jake.
Your mom's first love.
And her first ride
on a motorcycle.
I like to ride
in Jake's motorcycle.
Okay.
Jake also had
a thing for Tess.
For Grams?
All right, okay. Enough
humiliation for the night.
Harper, baby,
I made you a plate.
Here you go. You're too young
to be sad. Come on.
Well, being young
is overrated, Mama P.
Eat. You'll be fine.
Use the tongs.
Lily? Mind if I join you?
You know,
Anna lost her father
around the same age
that you lost your mother.
And then she had to deal with
my wedding to Ryan.
Cool.
And then you add to that
the complications of moving.
I'm here for you.
Sincerely.
With all due respect,
Dr. Coleman,
you're not my gran
or my therapist.
So, while I get your motive
for keeping us in LA,
I don't need your help.
Oh, no.
We used to be so cool.
- Hey, I'm still cool.
- I look amazing.
You're very cool. That song
you sent me was sick.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
I wish I had
more time to write.
But now all I do is
listen to parenting podcasts.
Well, I'm sorry for ruining
your exciting rock star life.
Harper, wait. I was just--
Wait, I wasn't serious.
Look, I gave up performing,
but I have you.
- Enjoy your party.
- You can't leave.
I don't think I belong
in here, Grams.
Let me handle this.
I've got you.
- Harper!
- Anna,
honey, you just need
to pause and reframe.
- Thanks, Mom.
- What?
- What did I do?
- I was handling it.
And you completely undermine
me as a parent.
I was trying to help you.
Well,
your help isn't helpful.
Well, that's not
very nice to say.
Can the great and mysterious
Madame Jen
interest you ladies
in a psychic reading?
No.
Thank you very much,
but, um,
right now is not the...
Time?
- It's just not really our...
- Thing?
This will all be over soon,
if you just...
- Go with it.
- Go with it. Yes, exactly.
- Come on in. Yes. Yes.
- No. No.
- Come.
- Okay, I'm coming. Here we go.
- Anybody else interested?
- Let's try this out.
I do discounts
for bigger groups. Okay?
Okay. That's fine.
That's good.
And that's how I lost my spot
at the Larchmont
Farmers' Market.
But I did get a table
by the lids
and free milk counter
inside of the Starbucks.
So, I am a life coach,
but I also do Reiki.
If you notice,
I have several business cards,
because I actually have
a business-card-making
business.
So, that's the card for that.
Uh, I can put quotes on there
that I can just make up
for you.
If you want something
inspirational, for example,
I can make up
a quote like, um...
"Live your life...
gosh dang it."
- Okay.
- So, here's--
And-And-And I'm gonna read
your palms now.
- 'Cause that's--
- Really?
Okay. And there they go. Yes.
Eenie, meenie, miney...
Hmm.
Okay. It smells like
you had some appetizers.
- Were they good?
- Good.
- Good. Yes.
- Yeah. Yes.
And did you have any, Mom?
- Um, no. Mm-mmm. No. I didn't.
- I'm-- No. No. Didn't--
- 'Cause I paid for them.
- I paid for them.
- It's a wedding. Okay.
- Okay. Okay, okay.
Your life lines. It...
It's like they've...
intersected before.
- How strange.
- Really?
You've walked
in each other's path.
It's like a crazy path-cross
that you've done.
You've learned a lesson.
A lesson that may
serve you again.
- Okay. That's enough.
- Thank you. Okay.
We'll give these
to my neighbors.
I'm onto something here.
One more thing.
Right over there is a QR code
that you can tip me with.
Any amount is appreciated.
Really.
I didn't know
I could do that voice.
- Nice prank. Ha-ha.
- Yeah, we know what you did.
What did I do?
What do you mean? The psychic.
- Yeah. Telling her about--
- What-- Okay, okay.
You think
I'd rather solve your problem
than deal with my booming
culinary empire.
♪ I just thought
Think about ♪
♪ All the things you can
And can't get ♪
- I'm following you because--
- You're happy here, so...
Are you the psychic?
I need you to
look into my future
and tell me where
we're going to live.
Oh.
Cool Gen Z talking to me.
If it's not London, I need you
to alter my destiny.
And I literally have to
stay in Los Angeles,
so, if there's--
Well, that's not really
how it works.
Well, how does it work?
Girls, follow my aura.
Boop. Beep.
You don't have
a lot of lines in your hands,
so it makes it harder for me.
You two are called
to be family.
- Yeah, right.
- Don't remind me.
A lesson for you all.
I see it now.
Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong.
Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong.
Change the hearts
you know are wrong...
Why is she rhyming
like a bridge troll?
Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong.
- Change the hearts...
- Earthquake.
Earthquake?
♪ Here and now ♪
Did you feel that?
Yeah, I...
It must be the dancing.
Yeah, right.
We're just freaking ourselves
out for no reason.
- Yeah. It's just in our heads.
- Right.
With your surf forecast...
All cozy and tucked in?
Fearless prediction
for the full moon tonight--
You need anything?
What more
could I possibly need?
How about sleeping
in our own beds
in our own rooms?
- Hmm.
Sweet dreams.
Teenagers.
I was one once.
Yeah, so was I. Twice.
- Night.
- Night. Love you.
Love you too, honey.
Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong.
Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong.
I don't have an alarm.
Why do my hands look so dry?
Why am I so tired?
Mom?
-  Grams?
- Grams?
Grams. Grams, are you okay?
Why are you
bloody waking me up for?
- Are you mad?
- Mad?
Why do I sound like this?
Sound like what?
American!
Oh. Good. Mom.
What was that?
Ow! Oh. Ow!
Lily, are you okay?
I'm not Lily.
Are you Harper?
No.
No. No. No, no, no.
- I'm bloody decomposing!
- Oh, my.
Harper?
- Oh, my God.
- Whoa.
- What is happening?
- I know.
It's me, Harp. It's Mom.
What are you saying?
So if you're me and I'm you,
then... then who is that?
I'm Grandma, sweetheart.
Oh, my gosh! I've died.
I killed myself!
She just has crevices
all over her face.
Look at the crevices.
My hands look like doll hands.
My butt feels so high.
I think I just peed a little.
Oh, no.
My face
feels so thirsty and dry.
My face is perfect.
My face
looks like a Birkin bag
that's been left out
in the sun to rot.
Why?
Why do I have to pee again?
This is so much weirder
than the last time.
Last time? What last time?
How come you never told me?
We never told anyone,
sweetheart. Overnight oats.
Now let's just pause
and reframe.
No. I didn't want to be
a part of this family
and now I'm part
of some dodgy family curse?
- And I'm the eldest?
- Mom.
And where are her lips?
She has no lips!
Where did they go?
How do we fix this?
Well, you know, last time,
we switched back
when we saw things
from the other's perspective.
Should we hold hands?
- Hold my hands.
- Well, we can--
- Just...
- Yeah.
I know I've been hard
on you and Eric,
but I can now see that
you're doing the right thing.
And, Mom, you have always done
so much for me, and I see you.
I see you.
- Are you really seeing me?
- Mm-hmm. I really see you.
Because I don't feel anything.
You have no idea how hard
I'm seeing you right now.
- One, two, three.
- ...three.
Girls, that doesn't work.
Yeah, we tried that last time.
Looking like this
is why people like you
become shut-ins,
and what's with this accent?
"Tomato."
Is that what you think
I sound like?
Oh, my God, yes.
Of course this is
what you sound like.
- Let's go to Erewhon...
- I do not sound like that.
I've never said that.
I don't even know...
Then I need to
call my energy healer
because I need a chakra reset.
- That's what you sound like.
- The healer.
Madame Jen.
I thought she was a psychic.
Ow. I thought she did
sound baths for dogs.
I thought she was
a water sommelier.
She did try to sell me knives.
What? No, well,
whatever she is,
we have to find her,
but until then...
"Until then" what?
Last time
we convinced everyone
that we were each other
until we switched back.
Oh, brilliant. So how are we
supposed to pull that off?
Well, panicking is not
going to help anyone!
- I need you to get dressed.
- This sucks!
- Go. Go get--
- No! Stop.
Bye, girls.
It's going to be great.
Look, Mom.
I kept it totally together
in front of the girls,
but I have to be honest,
I am freaking out right now!
That was you
keeping it totally together?
Yes!
No, no. Just checking.
Aura photographer.
Hmm. Twenty percent off
on her Etsy shop.
I can't get married.
I haven't even
had a boyfriend yet.
We have to switch back
to our bodies.
At least your body
didn't wake up with arthritis.
It's disconnected.
I guess her life coaching
business went bust.
I'm supposed to get married
this weekend.
What are these?
And how many puffer jackets
does someone need?
- Hmm. Reiki master.
- What? What'd you find?
I bent down and didn't toot.
Youth really is wasted
on the young.
And what's with the old
tissues in every pocket?
Explain.
No answer at Reiki. Now what?
Did you try
her vegan meat loaf truck?
They don't have a number,
and they only use DoorDash,
and I don't know
how to do that.
I look
Eileen Fisher years old.
I'm literally my mother.
I'm going to need therapy
for the rest of my life
and not the kind from Grams.
Like the real kind
that you have to pay for.
Why does anyone wear these?
Did she say anything,
like a fortune?
No, but maybe
she told the girls.
Did the psychic say anything
to you about a fortune?
It could be the key
to getting out of this.
- Wait, she did, right?
- She did.
What was it?
"Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong."
That's about our
parents getting married.
LA. London.
As teenagers,
we have no power.
No say in whether we move
or stay, but as adults...
Mom, she didn't
say anything to us!
Oh.
Whoa. Anna. Anna!
You do not hit me.
I am your mother, young lady.
- So, what do you say?
- Well, then...
- It's not working!
- We need a plan.
Not my fault!
- DK doughnuts!
- She'll love those.
- Harper, got 'em.
- I... I'll love them.
Hey, girls.
How was the sleepover?
- Good.
- Very good.
- We did teenager stuff.
So here's our plan.
First,
these clothes are rubbish.
I just can't.
Can you just give me
five minutes?
- What?
- Oh, no.
How? Why?
You're in your mum's body,
so all you have to do
is tell my dad
you don't love him anymore.
Wedding is off. Done.
Whoa. Got some bangs.
- What did you do to my hair?
- I fixed it.
And you're welcome.
- It's called a fringe.
- Fixed it.
You don't seriously think
you're going to my work
dressed like this.
Take that off.
You're going to get me fired.
- What'd you do to my hair?
- I straightened it.
You never wash your hair.
No, I don't.
The ocean washes it for me.
Obviously,
the wedding can't happen.
It's Friday.
We only have till Sunday.
We gotta do
some serious sabotage.
The immigration interview,
the rehearsal lunch.
Then what if we cancel
all the wedding stuff?
The cake, place, people.
Yes, and all we have to do
is convince our parents
that they are incompatible.
Which should not be hard
because my mom obviously
should not be with some
wannabe Gordon Ramsay.
Well, my father
doesn't want to be
with some wannabe
Valley Village rocker mom.
I quite like this, sexy tiger.
- Doughnut!
- It's, um...
It's an American superstition
that it's bad luck
for the bride and groom
to kiss
before they say I do so...
Really? For how long?
For a long time.
A long, long time.
- Really?
- Yeah. Also, uh...
no touching hands.
No touching at all.
No gazing
into each other's eyes
because it's gross. Um, yeah.
- How odd.
- For maximum luck.
And finally,
we must be convincing as them
until we break them up.
Lily?
- What?
- Yeah?
Did you
just take Tess's calcium?
Mmm.
Bone health.
You need those.
- You need those.
- Yes, I'll be taking them.
Okay.
- You need to take those.
- Give me the doughnut back.
- No. You're very diabetic.
- Okay, girls.
Let's crack on.
- Oh.
- Um...
Well, actually, uh, Lily and I
aren't feeling very well.
We think it might be a...
My throat.
...smart decision
to stay home.
This has nothing to do
with your detention?
Oh. Uh...
Well, you wouldn't want me
to go to school sick,
would you, Mom?
Hmm.
You don't feel sick to me.
Does she look sick
to you, Grams? I mean, Mom?
No. They look fine.
You have your client Ella's
huge Rolling Stone
photo shoot today
and your immigration
interview.
Don't you need a little bit
of help with that, hmm?
Of course she needs your help.
Right? Kids these days.
They'll say anything
to get out of school.
- All right. Come on. Let's go.
- Go on. And make good choices.
- See you at the dance studio!
- Bye! What?
Dance studio?
Let's go. Change at the club.
I've got your bag.
Change?
This is the finals.
Welcome, everybody,
to the Westside
Pickleball Championship.
Yeah. You have
your championship today.
I think you're gonna be late.
Late? Yes!
Yeah, I'm gonna be late.
Okay, newlyweds,
you just made
your grand entrance
into the wedding reception.
The lights begin to dim.
And a five, six, seven, Eric.
- Beth, no.
- Oh, right. Like a bull.
Yes!
- Charging. It's a bull. Yes.
- Stallion.
Get it, groom.
Big stallion energy.
- It's a bull, though.
- All right.
- So look at him.
- What?
Eye contact, come on.
- Hi.
Tango is your pelvis.
Pickleball.
It's a sport like tennis
but it is pathetic.
Tennis for lazy people,
that's what it is.
It's like tennis
but for nonathletes.
It's a bunch of old nutters
with giant paddles
chasing a Wiffle ball.
It's not bloody Wimbledon,
is it?
Here we go.
- That's yours!
- Okay. That was so fast.
Oh, so aggressive!
- What was that?
- She almost hit me!
- Oh.
- Okay.
- No. You're going down.
- Up. Up you go.
- I think you should go up.
- No, it's okay. It's fine.
This is good right here.
You're just lying
on the floor.
Taking a little nappy-poo.
It's not a nappy-poo,
it's tango.
Oh, no. I'm just thinking that
maybe tango isn't our dance.
- Um, anything else?
- Beth, what else is sexy?
Come on. Let's keep
our head in the game.
- Whoo!
- Game point, suckers.
Drop in!
Serena Williams,
she's got nothing
on the sounds
these ladies are making.
The body-thumping beat
of hip-hop.
- Like that? Yep.
- Bop, bop, bop. Yes.
A hop and a hip-hop.
I've never seen this kind
of hip-hop.
- She's on the ground.
- How is she doing that?
That's a new move.
That's defensive offense.
Defensive offense!
Woman, get up!
Oh, no!
- That was close!
- Wow! Did you see that?
Did you see that?
Did we win?
Yes! Yes!
We won!
I believe that was illegal
and I'd like to roll back
the tapes
and watch that one more time.
Take that, boomers!
- Okay. You know what, no.
- Okay, first of all--
- Hold me back.
- You stay back.
- We are not boomers.
- We're Gen X!
- We are elder millennials.
- Some of the last millennials.
- The finale.
And five, six, seven, eight.
Go! And slide. That's it.
Get it.
To the side. Whoo!
Get it. Yes!
Ow!
And Anna.
- Run, girl.
- Run!
Anna.
- Come on, let's go.
- Run!
- Get it. Run. Run.
- Run.
Anna.
Mom, we're supposed
to know where to go.
Act natural, honey.
- Detention's that way.
- Can you tell... Okay.
I have
an immigration interview,
a rehearsal lunch,
Ella’s big show, my wedding,
and I am stuck in detention!
Well, I'm stuck here too.
And it's the championships
for the entire Westside.
Well, well, well.
Look who showed up.
Lily Reyes and Harper Coleman.
How have you not retired yet?
The school had our pension
invested in crypto
but since I'm not supposed
to complain about it,
per my lawyer,
it's neither here nor there.
So let's surrender our devices
Let's go.
- Mr. Bates... Come on.
- We just got our phones back.
- That's right. We love school.
- Here.
Thank you, Simon.
And now it's time to prepare
for the most boring task
you could ever
possibly imagine.
Sit there, read or think only.
No screens, books.
Wait.
Does he mean hours
of uninterrupted peace?
Wipe that look of bliss
off your face.
Get over yourself, Elton.
This is high school,
not prison.
Yeah, it's not a prison.
Which, FYI, research shows
is ineffective
at preventing recidivism.
Yeah, "resisism".
You know, giving back
to the community
is a lot more effective
than trapping people inside.
Oh!
You wanna go outside?
Let us out.
- Yeah, let us out.
- Let us out.
Let us out. Let us out.
- Let us out. Let us out.
- Outside.
Move it! Let's pick it up!
Out of the way!
We need to find
Madame Jen, now.
We need our phones.
Come on, Reyes!
You run like my grandma.
- Pick it up.
- Rude!
Pick up the pace
or you'll pick up trash.
It's in two days.
Yeah, I know. I don't care
about the deposit.
- And the officiant?
- That includes the officiant?
Cancel that, too. Thank you.
Call from Jett. Answer it?
Is this for real? Yes.
Where are you?
The editor
from Rolling Stone is here.
- Come on! Hurry up!
- Oh, no.
Remember,
it's the Hungry Tour.
Trevor's allergic
to strawberries.
Look sweet, Ella.
- Ella's having a meltdown.
- Morning, Anna.
Hello, my staff of people
that I see all the time.
Can you sign off on the dress?
Here's your juice.
- Oh, thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
All right, so she's over here
by this...
- Girl, what?
- Ugh.
- Why would you give me that?
- You yell at me if I don't.
Anna. Jean shorts, rash guard.
Laundry day?
Let's talk about
the headline for the article.
"It's giving It-Girl.
Pop star queen Ella
slays down the house."
- Wait, what?
- Or,
"We're gagging, besties.
Ella's new album
just hits different."
No, no. Just stop.
What deeply out-of-touch
old person came up with those?
- You did.
- I did? Wow.
Thanks, puss.
Okay, I really need you
to focus on Ella--
Okay.
Do something.
Ella?
Trevor unfollowed me.
And you know what that means?
No.
What it means is that
the whole world knows
that he dumped me.
It's everywhere!
Okay. I am your manager,
so I'm gonna manage this.
Okay.
Ryan,
I really do need to dash.
But they said the photographer
is back in 5 minutes.
Photographer?
Yeah.
For your new passport photo.
The one you need for
the international part
of your book tour?
Oh, yes.
I remember every detail
that you told me about me.
Yeah. I got prescriptions,
you got the essentials.
Essentials?
Yes.
Do I need all these things?
I need that. Yes.
Where does this go?
What? Adult nappies?
That is so lazy.
- Oh, hey.
- Yes. Right here.
- Fixodent?
- Yes.
Isn't that toothpaste
for old people?
No. This is for when
you lose your teeth.
I'm gonna lose my teeth?
No!
Okay, slowpokes.
I want every blue spirulina
smoothie spill gone.
I want every
chia seed scraped.
Every chewed piece
of organic gum
on the bottoms
of these seats gone!
Way to go, Harper.
Use your nails if you have to.
What?
No, this was Lily's fault.
Elton.
Yeah?
I understand that you
feel the need to prove a point
because I publicly undermined
your authority.
Oh!
Do you understand me?
This isn't
restorative justice.
I mean, if anything,
you're making these kids
want to act out more.
How does Lily always manage
to make things worse?
It's a unique talent.
I have connections
on the school board, Elton.
Well, you're a stupid kid
and you have no connections,
but you have earned,
along with everybody here,
three more weeks of detention.
- Oh, my...
- Lily!
- Bro!
- Your royal highness.
- Come on!
- My God!
That was uncalled for.
Let's all take a deep,
centering breath.
Meditate on this!
Take a deep breath
of this trash.
You ready?
Stunning.
Wow.
Good, right?
I think you're having
an allergic reaction.
No, no, no, no.
It's lip plumper.
I'm gonna get some ice.
Okay, give me the ring light.
And every bottle of Benadryl
I can find.
It's lip plumper. No, Ryan.
I don't have allergies.
Oh. Okay, whatever.
Do you have another
ring light?
- Like, a big ring light?
- Sure.
- And another thing. Can you...
- Yeah, okay.
You hold the ring light.
I'll pose. Okay, ready?
I got it.
Let me look. Hold on.
Oh, no.
Just 10, maybe 15 more.
I'll give you looks, okay?
All right, here I go.
"Dear Sir, must cancel
the wedding venue
because the bride is horrible,
as my daughter
always suspected."
Who's Laura?
Hello, hello.
Hey, hon. I need your
approval on the author photo.
- Okay.
- Texting it over now.
Oh, no. No, no.
That one's rubbish.
I just took a new one.
- I'm sending now.
- Thanks.
Oh, look. Her phone has
the giant letter virus.
Ryan. Is it possible for you
to drop me at Anna's work?
Hey, you Trevorheads.
That was your boy,
Trevor Travis,
with his brand-new song,
"Better than the Last One."
My mom's biggest client
is having a meltdown.
- Jett!
- I'm working!
Trevor, her boyfriend,
dumped her.
Trevor Travis?
She's so much better, better
Better than the
Last one
And they just got
matching tattoos.
That is literally
the worst thing
I have ever heard happening
to anyone ever, full stop.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Anna's getting married,
so she doesn't get
what it's like
to have your heart broken.
I know. When I was your age,
my mom--
I mean,
I had this boyfriend, Jake,
and all my friends say
he was my first love.
Is that who your song's about?
What song? My song?
♪ See you in my dreams ♪
♪ Whenever you go
I tear at the seams ♪
I wrote that?
It's really good.
This is a great song.
You're really good.
I don't get
why you quit playing.
Because I had a kid
who I probably resent since
I'm writing songs in secret.
So, you miss performing?
I mean, yeah, probably.
I'm finding out a lot
about myself today.
Anna, your song
is the only song I loved
out of everything
that we got sent.
I know you already said no,
but can I please sing it
at the Wiltern tomorrow?
I mean, it's your concert,
your tour.
You should sing
whatever song you want.
Okay. Yeah, just--
I feel like between managers
and stylists
and execs and label people,
I feel like I never get a say
in anything that goes on.
Right?
Right, because old people
never listen.
I mean,
people like you think--
I think people like me
think people like you
don't know any--
- You know what I mean.
- Yeah.
I have control over
my own life.
Absolute control.
Photoshoot's back on.
Photoshoot is back on,
grasshoppers.
Chop, chop, chop.
Let's make some fierce photos
of this fierce girl
right here.
Bruh, having a job
is really hard.
- Wait.
- What? "Wait" what?
If your mum wrote that song
about that Jake...
Yeah.
...that's how we can get our
parents to split up forever.
So if she is with him,
she can't marry my dad.
Well, how do we find him?
It's like a database
of old people.
- Jake. Yes.
- That's him from the photo.
Wait, wait, wait, look.
Okay.
And he owns
the Record Parlour.
He has liked
all your mum's posts.
He is proper obsessed
with her.
Single. Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
But first,
your mum must look fit
if she's gonna run into
the love of her life.
And I need to change, too.
Ella's stylist has pulled
the most gorgeous garms
I’ve ever seen
in my entire life.
Do we love this for me?
Girl, the label
loves this for you.
- Can we just put it on your--
- No.
- Maybe on your shoulder?
Rest it on your head?
Please, can we just
put our differences aside
so that I can
live my dream? Please.
This is only because
of the plan.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
It's not very me.
Harper. This is so exciting.
So, posing for the camera,
it's very different.
Find a shape and then hold it.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Good luck.
- Where did the fruit go?
- I'm s--
Oh, this is cool.
- Oh, that is chic.
- It's recycled I think.
'Cause I'm a pop star.
- Pop out.
- Yeah.
Pop.
No! No! No! No!
No, no, no.
Oh.
Tess, your styling
is so on point.
You two are the coolest adults
I have ever met.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- My mom does have a cool job.
- Yes.
Think she's
our new best friend?
I think so. I think so.
Do you guys need a ride?
- Oh, yes. Totally. Yes.
- OMG, yes.
Attention, students.
You'll be happy to know that
my anaphylactic shock
has subsided.
Yes. I didn't die.
Thank you.
And I hope
those who were involved
in that food fight
are loving detention.
Oh, no.
They've gone completely rogue.
Whoo!
- Yeah!
- This is so cool!
What are we wearing?
They're on a joyride
with Ella.
We'll never find them.
No, but we can find
Madame Jen.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Oh, yeah.
- ♪ Every boy and every girl ♪
- ♪ Spice up your life ♪
Madame Jen said
she lost her table
at the Larchmont
Farmers Market,
but now she can be seen at the
Starbucks across the street
from the Larchmont Village
wine and cheese shop.
Look, I know
we don't have time...
But we are here.
And my metabolism is
the speed of sound.
♪ Spice up your life ♪
I got extra whipped cream!
My knees work!
I haven't had real dairy
since Bush was president.
Curly fries!
Flexibility!
♪ If ya know
That you feel fine ♪
Mmm.
We really need to
find Madame Jen.
Yes, but they have onion rings
on their burgers.
I haven't digested
like this in decades!
I'm still not full!
Sugar.
Remember sugar?
But after this,
back to the mission.
Mmm. It has my full attention.
All you have to do is go
in there and flirt with Jake,
and remind him why he fancied
you when you were young.
Wait, I wasn't me
when I was young.
And I don't know how to flirt.
And I definitely don't know
how to flirt as an old person.
What do they do, talk about
transitional lenses?
Home repairs? John Mayer?
- I... I don't know.
- Oh! I have an idea.
We both wear our AirPods.
That way you can help me
because you have
a French boyfriend.
So you definitely know
how to flirt.
Yeah... Defo. Yes.
I'm gonna go in, and then
I'll give you the word
when to come in and make
your sexy grand entrance.
What sexy grand entrance?
What do you mean?
You have to be sexy.
- How?
- Like...
Sexy.
I'm not doing that.
Oh.
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ Take me back
The way that I was ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ You know I only tried to
Play your games ♪
♪ So you cannot
Forget my name ♪
♪ You and I are not the same
You always had it easy ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ Take me back
The way that I was ♪
♪ The way that I was ♪
Hey!
- This is a different look.
- Yeah. Uh-huh.
It's awesome. I didn't know
you were coming by today.
- I got the stuff in the back.
- What stuff?
What do you mean?
That's him.
That's her bloke.
What's happening?
He's going to get me stuff.
What is your mother doing
behind my father's back?
No. Hey, hey, hey!
- Do not shush me. Okay?
- Get down.
- He can't hear me.
- Get down. I'm ignoring you.
Hey, thanks again
for doing this.
What exactly are
we doing here?
Signing the merch
for the charity auction.
Oh.
- Right.
- Here you go.
Right. The merch.
Oh!
I have a question.
Do you ever think about me?
About us?
I'm not sure there's a right
answer to this question.
I mean, do you ever miss us?
You're getting married
this weekend.
Unless I'm not.
Okay, very good.
Now, do something cheeky.
Like, flip your hair.
Good.
Ooh, good. Big, big,
big moves. Big moves.
One more. Shake your head.
Shake it.
More. Like,
all the way around.
There you go. Shake it.
Excellent.
Okay, um, wink at him.
Try winking. Wink.
Wink.
Wink. One eye. One eye.
Now do both.
Wink. Okay, good.
Okay. Um, that's not working.
Um... Uh... Oh!
Bite your lip. Bite your lip.
Why is he looking at you
like that?
I'm biting my lip.
No, not your top lip.
Your bottom lip.
Bite your bottom lip.
Like that, pouty.
I know what this is.
I've seen this before.
You're having a stroke.
- Mm-mmm. No, no.
- We need to get you help.
I just need to go to
the bathroom.
I just... Yeah.
Gotta go to the bathroom.
- Uh, it's in the back.
- All right. I'll find it.
Are you sure? I...
There's no merch in the--
I was really bad at that.
So bad at that.
How do you know
your boyfriend liked you?
You just know.
Huh?
How? Like, specifically.
You've dated a guy.
You know this.
You have experience.
Tell me. Help me out here.
Harper, I... I don't have
a French boyfriend.
My entire dating experience
is watching 500 hours
of Love Island.
Wait, you're, like, the most
confident person I know.
It's an act.
What?
Well, you're not gonna
tell everyone, are you?
No. I'm not like that.
I wouldn't do that.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh! You're not gonna hug me,
are you?
No, I was... Just...
- No, don't do that.
- Okay, it was just...
All right, look, no, we should
get back out there. Right?
Because, otherwise,
he'll think I'm pooping.
- There she is!
- I see her. Right by the milk.
And I see your screenwriting
career taking off.
If you move over to, um...
- Genre?
- Genre, yes.
Genre.
Elevated genre?
Um...
No. Sorry.
- You!
- Um. Oh.
Um...
How can I help?
Take one wild guess.
Are you gonna serve me papers?
We switched bodies.
Oh!
Oh, my gosh.
It actually worked.
That's amazing.
It's never worked before.
Um, would you guys mind
leaving me a review
or, like, five stars?
And just saying, like,
"Oh, my gosh!
Madame Jen was so much fun..."
Tell us how to switch back
right now.
Okay. All right.
Um, I'll consider it
if you sign up for
my Reiki and
financial management package.
Tell us how to switch back,
you multi-hyphenate lunatic!
Oh, my gosh.
I am a multi-hyphenate.
That absolutely slays.
I'm supposed to get married
in two days.
Right, okay. Um...
All right. Well, you have to
look at the reading.
- That's the only way.
- We don't know the reading.
Um, what are you
talking about?
I said the reading
directly to you both,
multiple times,
in a scary whisper voice.
Because we weren't there.
That wasn't...
Right! Oh, right.
You weren't you
because you had switched
with the other women,
who are...
Okay, that's...
And it makes sense.
Um, okay. Well...
...the reading was,
"Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong."
- Didn't we try that?
- I think we tried that.
- We tried it.
- Okay, the problem is
your hearts might not be
the only ones
that need changing.
So...
Mmm. Cute.
Well, our time is up.
Wait, but...
No, no, no.
There's got to be something
else you can do, right?
I wish I could help you,
but my shift is starting.
So, what I can do for you
is get you a cortado,
an Americano, a...
...and any kind of espresso
or non-espresso drink.
It's your dad! Shoot!
This is all new inventory
that we need to get sorted.
Uh, excuse me.
- Tess?
- Oh!
What are you doing down there?
Stretching.
Ah. Yeah. I...
Anna didn't...
She didn't tell me that
you were gonna be here today.
- Oh!
- What interview?
I mean, yes, I know
the interview. Now?
I was just thinking
about you the other day.
Really?
I've been meaning to
ask you something.
Sure.
And, um, I don't quite know
how to broach the subject.
But is, um, your husband...
Is he still with us?
Yeah. I can't believe it.
I mean, he's so old.
How... How old is he?
We never talk about it.
Somewhere between 50 and 100.
Really.
Yeah. Yeah. But... Okay,
let me focus for a second.
I'm worried about Anna,
all right?
She's been being weird
with me,
and she keeps asking
if I ever think about her.
You know,
maybe she is reconsidering.
- Reconsidering?
- Uh-huh.
Three weeks ago, she told me
how in love she is with Eric.
Do you know that
she wrote a song about you?
- No.
- Anna!
Daughter.
Why don't you tell Jake
about the song you wrote?
I wrote a song about us.
You know what,
I'll give you your privacy.
I'm just gonna go look for
music for old people.
You know, really old,
like Coldplay.
It's nice to hear
you're writing again.
Yeah, can you just give me
a second, bro?
Just one second.
Coldplay...
We need to get to the
immigration interview. Now.
- Okay, let's go.
- Yeah.
Oh! My legs are so weak,
my knees are cracking
like walnuts.
What is happening right now?
My brain is telling my body
to stand up,
but it's like shouting into
the abyss.
See?
I just tried to get up again.
Okay.
- Help me. Help me up.
- Okay.
We have to find a way to get
to the immigration interview.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Wait, I have an idea. Come on.
So, that's why Tess
and I have a special bond.
Oh, Jake. Hi.
Could we borrow your car?
Oh, and don't worry,
we're totally of age to drive.
Anything for you, Dr. C.
You ready?
Hold on.
Whoo!
Oh, that's a woman
after my heart.
- I love driving!
- I don't wanna--
I don't know who taught you
how to drive
but they weren't good.
Wrong side! Wrong side!
Wrong side!
- Okay.
- You're gonna get us killed!
Oh, geez.
Oh! I can't look.
I can't look.
No, no.
I'm a very good driver.
That was smashing.
Whoo!
Oh!
Hi.
Hi. Nice car.
It's totally mine.
- You think he's cute.
- I do not.
- You totally do.
- Stop. I do not.
- Yes, you do. You do.
- I do not. Shut up.
She thinks you're cute!
I do not!
- Yes, she does.
- I do.
- She so does.
Thanks.
Dr. Coleman?
Oh, my gosh. Go.
That's my therapist!
You nervous?
Oh, why would I be?
We're perfect for each other.
You'll see.
Oh, that's cryptic.
Coleman/Reyes?
- Ah, yes. That's us.
- Go.
My love.
- So many ruffles.
- Yeah.
- There we go.
- Ah.
How are you?
Oh, um, I was just dumped
by my fiancé, so...
- You know.
- Oh, no.
I... I'm so sorry.
Oh, what a decent thing
to say. Thank you.
Yes, of course.
Are you single?
Kidding!
Um, can I see your paperwork?
- Ah, yes.
- Yeah.
I'm sure you're approved.
Wait. Whoa.
Don't you need to see
if we really know each other?
I mean, usually, yeah,
but he seems like
such a kind and honest man
who clearly works out.
- Oh.
- A lot.
I mean you could be a gymnast.
I did once qualify
to represent the UK
- in pole vaulting.
- You're kidding. Really?
I'd still like for us
to prove
that we, you know,
are marriage material.
So, what's my favorite
road trip snack?
Uh, 7-Eleven hot dog
dipped in blue Slurpee.
Dream vacay?
Taking the girls
to the Galapagos.
Harper would love
the biodiversity
and I think Lily could
really benefit from the dirt.
Though she really
just wants to see a, uh...
Komodo dragon in the wild.
It's her favorite animal.
These are too, too easy.
You gotta hit me
with the hard stuff.
What is my guilty pleasure
pump-up song?
Oh.
Uh, darling, I promised to
never divulge
that highly-classified
information.
See? He doesn't know me.
- At all. See?
- Okay.
We can't get married.
It's...
It's Chumbawamba.
She told you?
Wait. "Creepy Crawling"
or "Tubthumping"?
♪ I get knocked down
But I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
Keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down
But I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
Keep me down ♪
That's the one, yeah.
♪ Pissin' the night away ♪
Oh, wow.
♪ Oh, Danny Boy, Danny Boy ♪
♪ Danny Boy ♪
- Danny was my fiancé's name.
- Okay, enough.
What's my deepest,
darkest fear?
Oh.
That your love for Harper
and need to protect her
will push her away
rather than bring her close.
And then she'll run away
and be a surf bum
and then she'll get
a dodgy tattoo of the sun
around her belly button.
But you're a phenomenal mum
and Harper is amazing,
so that will never happen.
Well, that was really sweet.
I didn't know that.
You know, I approve
hundreds of marriages
that... ...probably
won't even last a year.
But you two...
- Thank you.
- Next.
Well done. We got approved.
Ugh.
Ugh, my seafood vendor says
we canceled.
- I should deal with this.
- Bet.
- Yeah, my mom's almost here.
- Okay.
Uh, bye.
What an odd mix-up.
Hop in, muppet. How'd it go?
Your dad knows a lot
about my mom.
- I think he really loves her.
- But did you do enough
to break them up?
I don't know.
I need to clear my mind.
- Can we go somewhere?
- Yes, yeah. Get in.
- Don't drive so fast.
- Okay. Buckle up!
"Change the hearts
you know are wrong
to reach the place
where you belong."
What do you think
she meant by that?
I think she made it all up,
but look on the bright side,
honey,
these scooters are
so much fun!
Why have we never
done this before?
Because you already have
one fake hip
and you do not need another.
Very funny. I'll have
you know, in this body,
I have two real hips.
Whoa!
Sorry. Sorry.
Nothing broke!
We're invincible!
Bone density!
I'm not exhausted!
Girls, get in the car.
How do kids get away
with anything anymore?
You know, I hated you
a little less today.
I think it's hard to hate me
when I look like your gran.
And...
I hated you
a little less today too.
I just don't understand how
anyone can dislike California.
It's, like, a wrong opinion.
Harper, you can't have
a wrong opinion.
I mean, look around.
Yes. Okay, Harper,
it's lovely.
It's lovely.
I just...
...I miss England.
We can talk about her
if you want.
No, thanks.
I think if I talk about her,
I'm giving away what little
of her I have left.
Okay.
And why are you so obsessed
that I like Los Angeles?
- Well, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
- No.
- Yes.
And look, even if I liked it
a little bit here, I mean...
You... You still
don't want me around.
- Obviously not.
I guess it's a good thing
we're stopping this wedding.
Yeah.
Where are they?
They're supposed to
be home by now.
This is very good.
A little dry.
Very fruit-forward.
And by fruit, I mean grapes.
Your lack of concern,
it's not working.
Just stay calm, honey.
Stay calm?
But I've got
the rehearsal lunch,
the final dress fitting,
and my wedding is in 36 hours,
and I'm trapped in the body
of a ninth-grader.
I did.
- I told you she approved it.
- You most certainly did not.
What difference
does it make, anyway?
- It's done now.
- Where on earth have you been?
- Oh.
- Well.
Can't two adult women
come home when they please?
What do you think you're doing
driving around
like that with Ella all day?
Ella needs to talk to you,
by the way.
You need to give her
more attention.
Why am I dressed like that?
I need more attention
from you sometimes.
She has a lot of stuff
to talk to you about.
She was crying.
Okay, I don't care
about that right now.
Did you make it
to the immigration interview?
Yes, I did.
Just, like, chill, okay?
Or do your weird
breathing stuff that you do.
Chill?
I am the adult here.
I'm in charge.
Doesn't look like it.
You just earned yourselves
a consequence.
- Ooh. No.
- Oh, no.
Give me your phones.
- Sure.
- No.
Psych.
By the way, you're the reason
this is all falling apart.
Shut up. No, I'm not.
Yes, it totally is.
And don't...
Girls, this is serious.
We all need to
start getting along
unless we want to be
stuck like this forever.
You know, you lot are getting
the better end of this deal.
It's us who are gonna be dead
in, like, five years.
She's 37.
I'm 36 and a half!
While you two
were out having fun,
we found Madame Jen.
And she made us buy
business cards for everyone
and a Reiki ten-pack!
What even is Reiki?
Huh? What is it?
Stop talking about Reiki.
Well, Madame Jen said
to change your hearts,
so change
your freaking dang hearts.
It's the only way for us
to get out of this mess.
I'm switching to red.
Do you want one?
You're making Mommy
very stressed!
...use Reiki now!
♪ You think that I'll leave ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ I just keep on ♪
♪ Coming back ♪
♪ I'm your good
And I'm your bad ♪
♪ 'Cause you're my baby ♪
♪ Ooh, oh
'Cause you're my baby ♪
♪ Baby
Baby ♪
Okay, Blue Crush.
Look at you.
Shredding the waves, dude.
Never use those words again.
Wait, what are you doing here?
Our lessons.
What lessons?
Surf lessons.
But it looks like you're ready
to surprise Harper
and take her out.
Oh, yeah. That's really gonna
surprise Harper.
Obviously.
Oh, no, I just ate
a bowl of onions.
In the water?
Yeah, they keep me alert.
Okay.
Look, I know it feels like
we're in
an impossible situation.
Maybe that's why things have
felt a bit off with us.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, but Anna...
I think we should stay in LA.
What about Lily?
Going back to London,
to Pembridge Hall,
it's not going to
bring back her mum.
And there's no one
keeping us there anymore.
If I'm honest,
we've felt so lost.
So what she needs is
to be with family.
A gran like Tess,
a sister like Harper, and you.
What is it?
It's just...
I can't believe how much
you love me and my family.
It's a real, true love.
It's just... It's crazy.
Okay. Well,
you made it look so easy.
I'm gonna give it a go.
I don't know if that's--
Maybe I've improved
as much as you!
Oh!
I'm okay!
Oh.
No. I'm gonna wait.
I'm gonna wait
for the instructor.
I mean, you were amazing.
You were, like,
weaving and dodging,
and you're like a pro surfer.
- I'm glad we talked.
- Yeah, me too.
It's good we came to
a decision.
Yeah, dude.
Really good.
See you at
the rehearsal lunch!
Totally,
but my mom said I have to...
It fits perfectly.
Anna, come look.
Oh, wow.
Sweetheart...
...fix your posture.
This is weird.
Weirder for me, trust me.
Really? Are you the one
wearing your mom's
wedding dress?
Well, I never thought I'd get
to have this experience.
Especially like this.
Well, Mom, you know how
much I love to wear a dress.
Ugh. Sorry this
is such a mess, Harper.
Mom, there's something
I need to tell you.
What were you talking to
my dad about this morning?
Oh, we were just talking
about the lunch.
What about the lunch?
Just lunch stuff.
Oh, right. The lunch.
Okay. Um.
I'm just gonna make
a quick call.
Okay.
Oh, hi! It's Tess.
Um, listen, last minute
but Anna was wondering
if you might like to attend
her rehearsal luncheon.
No, no. You would not be
an imposition. You know what?
I think your appearance there
would make it
a much more lively affair.
So, I just wanted to
say that I'm very excited.
And being at my new restaurant
makes it all the more special
for all of us to finally
come together as a family.
So with that said,
welcome to Lily's.
Congratulations.
Thank you for coming.
Really, Eric and I
so appreciate it.
Oh.
Right. Thanks.
Champagne, ladies?
- Yes, please.
- 'Cause we're adults.
- Mm-hmm.
Girls, Eric's parents are here
so best behavior, please.
Stand up straight.
Good posture.
Anna, my soon-to-be daughter.
My heart is so full.
That's me.
How was your flight?
Oh, it was 13 hours and
30 minutes from Manila. Ugh.
Major jet lag.
Some worse than others.
But I really love it here.
Maybe Harper can
teach me the surf.
- Sure, dude.
- Mano po, Lola.
You're so silly.
Only Lily calls me Lola.
But I want to support
your Tagalog learning.
Keep it up.
Come on, Anna.
- Let's have a drink.
- No, no, no, no. We just...
We have to wait for
the surprise guest.
What are you talking about?
Oh, just wait.
- Hello, sir. Welcome.
- Ah, no, thank you.
- I'm here to see someone.
- Jake?
Just alone or...
What's he doing here?
I invited him
but I didn't think he'd come.
But, you know,
he really likes your gran.
My mom's gonna freak out,
- you know that?
- I know. So will my dad.
- That was the whole point.
- You...
Dr. C. Thank you
for inviting me.
I... I saved your number.
I hope that's okay.
Of course.
- Hi, there.
- Hey.
Hmm. I think I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
Uh, now?
But, uh, you know, your mom,
she really wanted me here.
Right. I'm sure.
Well...
Okay.
- I got you.
- Thank you so much.
- No, no, no. Wait.
- You're the best, bro.
- Wait!
- Thank goodness.
I will be right back.
- No. Jake, don't go.
- Ah, Tess. Tess.
- Yes?
- Uh, can we have a chat later?
- It's regarding Lily.
- Oh!
If it's regarding Lily,
we should chat now.
My big sister, Anna.
After every atomic wedgie
you gave me,
I always knew that you
also had an atomic heart.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Anna and I decided
we should all stay in LA.
What?
- Yes.
- What?
Everyone?
Yes.
As a therapist,
I was hoping to
get your thoughts
on the best way to
approach it with Lily.
But, I know how you feel
about billable hours
so we can chat later. Yeah?
Okay. Okay.
You bloody backstabber.
I know what you did.
- Shh!
- All right,
who wants to speak next?
Father of the groom
looks ready.
No, no. I have a few
choice words for the bride.
I would like to make a toast.
That's crystal.
Uh, we have
a toasting triangle.
- Oh, piss off.
- Okay.
I would like to make a toast
to your future husband
so that he knows
what kind of woman
he is getting married to.
He does, he does, he does.
He knows who he's marrying
and he can make
his own decisions
and he knows not to be
manipulated by other people.
Tess.
Hey, gramps,
this is between us.
Listen to your husband.
You listen to me.
Ugh, Ella. What does she want?
Micro cilantro
from the foothills of Oaxaca.
It was not my fault.
That micro cilantro
is bursting with flavor.
But it is your fault
that the cilantro
has no loyalty to...
- What are they doing?
- We have to stop them.
Are you doing all right, Harp?
Ella, this is
the last thing I need.
Oh, Jake's back already.
Jake? Who?
Jake, what...
What are you doing here?
- Uh...
- It was all her, I swear.
Hello. Um, and you are?
That's Anna's ex-boyfriend.
- What? Why?
- She invited her ex-boyfriend?
What?
Because she still
has feelings for him.
- Okay. That's not-- That...
- No.
- What? I...
- No. Uh...
After the appetizer,
Anna said she wasn't
feeling well so I went--
Right. I wasn't feeling well.
Okay, but not from
the food here.
The food is fine.
- Too fishy. No.
- It's fish.
It is not the food.
She's just on her period.
That's all.
She's on her period.
I'm on mine right now.
- I got it.
- I didn't know where
- you are in your cycle...
- I know, dude.
It's fine. Thanks.
Can someone please
explain to me
- what's going on here.
- I don't know.
- Let's just tell the truth.
- Don't let her.
She shouldn't explain anything
because she will just lie.
- Hey, me?
- She lies.
- Yeah.
- I trusted you.
I know, but you don't know
what he said to me.
You weren't there.
You didn't hear it.
I don't think
this marriage should happen.
Well, you know what? It's not
just about what you want.
It's about what she wants
and she wants--
It isn't ever about
what I want.
- It's always about you.
- That's enough.
Does everyone want this?
Okay, that's enough.
Well, yes. Some of them do.
Hey, that's enough!
The girls fighting
is one thing
but this is your mum.
And for some reason,
your ex-boyfriend is here.
Yeah.
Anna, I love you
but you're clearly
having second thoughts.
This isn't working
for our families,
and we always said
we'd put our families first.
So...
We can't do this.
I can't do this.
Lily, help your grandparents.
I'll meet you at the valet.
The wedding's off.
He's right.
It's over.
Wait, no.
Wait, please, please, please.
No.
I'm so sorry. I promise,
I didn't mean for this
to happen.
I think you did.
Well.
- I guess we did it.
- Yeah.
Uh...
I know this isn't
the best time
but can I have my car back?
Maybe later.
Mom!
She seems upset.
No, she just needs some space.
What about you?
Are you doing okay?
Oh, yeah. I'm always okay.
It would be fair
if you weren't.
That all got pretty crazy.
I worry what will happen
when Tess doesn't have
those two to drive her crazy.
You're worried about her?
I'm worried Tess would be
really lonely
if all of you moved to London.
You're a good guy, Ryan.
Thank you.
Go on.
Maybe this isn't
for me to fix.
Mind if I join you?
- Okay.
Are you okay?
I haven't seen my dad
that upset...
since my mum died.
And it was all my fault.
You know, when Ryan asked me
to marry him,
I thought a lot about
what Anna and Harry's dad
would have said.
How he would have felt
about it.
I think he'd be
so happy for us.
That we found someone
who loved us all so much.
I think my mum
would feel the same way.
Yeah.
- I really miss her.
- I know. It's okay.
She would be
so disappointed in me.
- No, no, no.
- Yes, she would.
Because I was very selfish.
I was.
No.
I was, and I know it.
No, she'd know your heart.
I just... I should...
- Find my dad...
- Yeah.
...and-- and apologize.
Ella, Ella, Ella.
Why are you
walking so fast?
I can't walk as fast as you.
Ella keeps texting me
the word "urgent,"
and her show starts,
like, now.
But what about Eric?
I think we should
go back, Mom.
I thought there was a way
to make everyone happy
but there's not, all right?
But I think that we should
go back for Eric.
- I really should--
- Come on. My client needs me.
Ella, Ella, Ella.
♪ You're my confidant ♪
♪ You're my underdog ♪
♪ You're the one I want ♪
♪ 'Til it's said and done ♪
♪ Call it delicate
All the benefits ♪
♪ Invisible string
When we separate ♪
Don't go! Stop the car!
- Tess?
- Don't go! Stop the engine!
I'm not.
The engine's not even on.
♪ You hold it down
When I'm lost and found ♪
♪ Look in my eyes
Be so profound ♪
♪ Don't need to say a thing
We lose or win ♪
♪ Together, you and me
We got everything ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ Yeah
We're going there anyway ♪
- Ella, he loves you!
- I love you!
♪ One fine day ♪
Cely, is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Okay.
I wonder what
the big emergency was.
♪ Happier, happy days ♪
♪ Right where I do belong ♪
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
Ella said you said
you missed performing.
I--
And that you told her
she could do
any song she wanted to.
You did?
Dressing room is right around
the corner. Put this on.
Why?
Well, because
we're not 15 anymore.
Dolphins.
- Get in there. Okay.
- What?
- Let me know when she's ready.
- Crazy.
I can't believe
you're making me do this.
Don't make fun of my dress.
♪ Night or daylight
Space or timeline ♪
♪ Chasing taillights
You and I ride ♪
♪ Open windows
'Til the light it burns ♪
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Lily and I tried to sabotage
you and Eric.
And I tried to make him
fall out of love with you,
but I couldn't because
he loves you so much.
And Mom, you shouldn't
have to give that up for me.
Just like you gave up
being a rock star.
And I know you've been
secretly writing songs
in private.
What?
You know, the one about Jake.
What are you talking about?
"I'm your good
and I'm your bad
'cause you're my baby.
And love was made to last."
Huh?
Harper, that song is not
about Jake.
That song is about you.
About me?
Of course it is...
Harp.
Mom, I'm sorry that I said
I wanted to stay
with Grams if you left.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry that I made you
think that you had to choose
between being together
or being at home.
I choose you every time.
Okay.
We gotta go.
Look, we look like a grown-up.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Where am I going now?
If you'll excuse me,
I have to go get Lily.
No, no, no, no. Please.
I know I said I didn't want
this wedding to go on,
but-but that's not true.
It's just not.
I...
I was scared.
And... and I think I realized
that I didn't wanna
share someone I love.
I appreciate that, Tess.
I do--
But... But wait. But please.
You still love Anna.
You still wanna get married.
- I--
- Do you?
- Do you love her?
I love Anna.
- Do you wanna marry her?
- I wanna marry Anna.
- But then what?
- But it's not about me!
Lily is the most important
person in my life.
And I worry every day
I'm messing up as a parent.
Okay? I am on my own.
I lost her mum, and I am
so scared of losing her.
So I have to put her first.
What if you were
right all along?
What if being here
with the Colemans
is exactly what she needs?
I thought so too.
But after all this,
I'm not sure.
I am.
I love you so much!
I have a little surprise guest
for you.
Give it up for one of
my favorite bands, Pink Slip!
No. Why are you guys
doing this to me?
- You all right?
- No, no, no.
No, Mom. I don't know
how to play guitar.
- It's all right, okay? I do.
- I can't. No.
This is a bad idea. No, no.
- Harper! Harper, go!
- No. No. No.
Pink Slip! Pink Slip!
Pink Slip!
My friend is gonna be singing
her brand-new song tonight!
- Anna.
- Mom, you suck.
- Huh?
- What are you doing?
- Oh.
Oh.
- Go like this.
- Like what?
Mm-mmm.
- You got this.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- No.
Mm-mmm. No.
Yes, you can.
Do you know what?
Wait. Can we--
Can we just...
Can we stop for a second?
Sorry. I just...
I wanna bring out the person
that I wrote this song for.
She means everything to me,
and I love her so much.
I know that family
isn't always easy,
but family is everything.
She also plays guitar
way better than me.
So please welcome
my daughter, Harper.
Ready to do this? Together?
Yeah.
♪ See you in my dreams ♪
♪ Whenever you go
I tear at the seams ♪
♪ If you think that I'll leave
Don't worry ♪
♪ I'll just keep on
Coming back ♪
♪ I'm your good
And I'm your bad ♪
♪'Cause you're my baby ♪
What are we doing here?
This is silly.
Anna and I are--
Are madly in love. I know.
We tried. We really did.
It's just not--
No, no, no, no. Please.
Just give us one more chance.
- Please.
- Just trust us.
I just--
Is... Wait, is that...
Is that Anna?
♪ Only I can ease the pain
'Cause you're my baby ♪
♪ Oh, 'cause you're my baby ♪
- Excuse me.
- ♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Are you in your head? ♪
Ella gave me these yesterday.
Come with me.
Come with me. Come on.
♪ ...and lay on the bed ♪
♪ I'm trying my best
Believe me ♪
♪ This isn't the first... ♪
- We get to be here.
- Yep.
♪ And it won't
Be the last time ♪
♪ I can't find the words ♪
♪ But making it work
Ain't easy ♪
Is Ella wearing one
of my designs?
It was Anna's idea.
♪ You can tell me
That you're scared ♪
♪And I'll run my fingers
Through your hair ♪
♪ 'Cause you come
To say you're sorry ♪
♪ For the thousandth time ♪
♪ I'll just keep on
Coming back ♪
♪ I'm your good
And I'm your bad ♪
♪ 'Cause you're my baby ♪
♪ And love was made to last ♪
♪ I'm your sunshine
I'm your rain ♪
♪ Only I can ease the pain
'Cause you're my baby ♪
♪ Oh, 'cause you're my baby
Baby, baby, baby ♪
Mom, I'll always
choose you too.
This family is
exactly where I belong.
Wait.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
Uh-huh.
Okay. All right. Let's just...
That's better.
Okay.
Thank you, Los Angeles.
And Eric, if you're out there
and you'll still have me,
I can't wait to marry you.
I can't wait to marry you too!
What?
I said yes!
Okay, well, whatever that was,
just get him up here.
Excuse me.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Did you know
she could do that?
Not at all.
♪ Yeah ♪
- We did it!
- Yes! You two did it.
You did it together.
- We did.
- I know.
Wherever my sister is,
it's where I want to be.
Me too.
♪ Get up, get out, move on
Move on, there's no doubt ♪
♪ I'm all wrong, you're right
It's all the same with you ♪
♪ I'm too thin, too fat
You ask why ♪
♪ So why, so why?
So why, so why? ♪
♪ On and on
And on and on ♪
♪ Don't wanna grow up
I wanna get out ♪
♪ Hey, take me away ♪
♪ I want to shout out... ♪
It's him! That's the guy!
- Excuse me.
- It's him!
♪ Away, away, away ♪
No, no, no.
I just need to get down.
- They still got it!
- Whoo!
♪ I wanna get out
Hey, take me away ♪
♪ I want to shout out
Take me away, away ♪
♪ Away, away, away ♪
No, I just need
to get down. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
♪ Same old start
Same old end ♪
♪ Turn my head... ♪
I can't believe
you just did that.
- I know.
- So what do you say?
Will you marry me?
One condition.
I'm kissing you early.
♪ No, we... ♪
♪ Don't have ♪
♪ To get emotional ♪
♪ You'll never love
Somebody like me ♪
You'll never love ♪
♪ You'll never love
Somebody like me ♪
♪ And you could be
Somebody I need ♪
♪ You'll never love
Somebody like me ♪
Hi, Jake.
Dr. Coleman.
Oh, this is-- this is Bess.
We just met, but, uh, there is
something about her.
- Yes. Nice dress.
- Thank you.
Did you hear that? Nice dress.
She likes your dress.
♪ You'll never love
Somebody like me ♪
You'll never love ♪
♪ You'll never love
Somebody like me ♪
♪ And you could be
Somebody I need... ♪
We'll go somewhere to eat
after this.
Thanks for coming, everybody.
- I see.
- Sure, Mom.
- All right.
- Here we are.
Whoo!
Wait.
Girls! What did you do?
It's called lip plumper.
Run.
It-- It could be worse.
- It could be worse, you know.
- It could not be worse!
I mean... It's okay.
Just testing out a new look.
Camera's A marker.
Hi, everybody.
Welcome to Freakier Friday.
What? Ryan, I'm fine.
I don't need Benadryl.
I can't...
It's so good, you can't do it.
- What?
- Huh?
What?
That's the right "banana-na."
- No, no, no. Banana.
- Banana.
I have Mystery Date.
Truth is, I bet you
the dud is very hot now.
I see.
Are we talking
about a board game?
Jamie just turned
around like this.
She was like this.
- Mom?
- Yes?
You know, last time...
Okay, I'm locking in.
We have to find her.
But until then--
Until then, what?
I don't know why
I keep going...
♪ Pissin' the night away ♪
I can't. Sorry.
♪ Danny Boy ♪
Okay, Jamie,
reach for the enema box.
Mm. Mmm.
Mmm.
She's had 29 doughnuts.
Just give me the doughnut.
You're prediabetic.
What's that?
Not supposed to eat those.
You learned a lesson.
My God, I could be
a pirate, huh?
Oh, you fancy that?
Put on my jumper, eat my---
I can't!
You wanna fight?
I can fight too.
Let's fight!
Oh, my God.
Let us out!
- Do you want to be fired?
- It's a hit.
Anna Louise Coleman,
do you think--
Is that my middle name?
Yes, it is your middle name.
That's different.
What's that?
The pink Power Ranger?
I'm kidding.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Let's not.
Let's not. Let's not.
Oh, my God!
What the hell is she?
Was that a Pepto Bismol
comm... What is she doing?
Here we are. In the pelvis.
Like peanut butter molasses.
- Yes.
- Peanut butter molasses.
Slow.
Were any of those teenagers
a "Bad Boss Betty"?
No. I'm sorry.
Good. More.
That really was so bad.
What are you
doing down there?
Just crawling.
Look at the road!
Oh!
- I got caught!
- Cut!
That was fun.
Thank you for watching.
We love you so much.
- Thanks for coming.
- I think I just peed.
Okay, cut.